digitalfamily.com 2013-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Web Design Training courses, videos & tutorials at DigitalFamily.comWeb Design Training courses, videos & tutorials at DigitalFamily.com

DigitalFamily.com  **(referred to as “us” or “we” or “DigitalFamily.com” or “DigitalFamily”),**  is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

Because we do gather certain types of information when you purchase goods from us or sign up for mailing lists or special features, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the gathering and use of that information. This Privacy Policy explains what we collect, how we use it, and how our visitors can correct or change it.

This Policy discloses the privacy practices for the entire Artesian Media, Inc. network of sites, which includes DigitalFamily.com, ArtesianMedia.com, JCWarner.com, ChocolateGameRules.com, SipsFromtheFirehose.com, California Wildlife Photography site, and others, even those that are not listed here.

DigitalFamily,com is owned by Artesian Media, Inc. a private company that was created by Janine Warner and David LaFontaine.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [Janine@DigitalFamily.com](mailto:Janine@DigitalFamily.com) for clarification.

**What information does Digital Family gather/track?**

We collect two types of information about our site visitors: aggregated “traffic data” derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites using Google Analytics; and personal data that some visitors provide through optional, voluntary participation in our Reader’s Corner, by signing up for our email newsletter, by ordering book, videos, or other products, or through email messages sent to any of the email addresses included on any of the Artesian Media sites.

We collect traffic statistics and other information and use it to tailor our content to our users’ needs, as well as to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. We sometimes share the _aggregated_ demographic information with our advertisers and partners., but we  _never_  share any information about specific individuals with any third party.

> **Email**
> 
> Users of the Digital Family, or Artesian Media, Inc. sites may voluntarily e-mail us from time to time with requests for information and questions about the books, videos, and anything else.
> 
> Digital Family and Artesian Media, Inc. reserve the right to use the contents of emails we receive in any way, including by publishing the contents of those email messages on any of our sites. We make a good faith effort to remove any identifying information from emails before posting their contents.
> 
> **Email Newsletter**
> 
> ****DigitalFamily collects email addresses when visitors sign up for the email newsletter. We may also add your name to our mailing list when you make a purchase or send email to any of our staff or consultants. When we send out bulk email we use a third-party email service, MailChimp. We use this service because it is our understanding that MailChimp manages our mailing list and messages in compliance with all bulk email regulations and laws.
> 
> **Readers Corner  
>  **Visitors may voluntarily choose to gain access to the Readers Corner at DigitalFamily.com to access the templates, images, and other materials that complement our books, videos, and other products.  Information submitted during the process of gaining access to the Readers Corner may include the user’s name and other contact information in addition to his or her e-mail address. We reserve the right to use the contents of these submissions to contact users directly, on occasion, or to add you to our email newsletter mailing list, but always with an easy eay to opt-out option.
> 
> **DigitalFamily Store**  
>  When you place an order through the DigitalFamily.com; we request your name, address, and phone number as part of the transaction. Because we use third-party transaction services (Google Checkout and PayPal), we do not collect credit card information directly at DigitalFamily.com. We use Google Checkout and PayPal because we understand that they protect your private bank, credit card, and other information with advanced Internet security technology and that they will not share it with third party. You can learn more about the [Google Checkout Privacy Policy here](https://checkout.google.com/files/seller/privacy.html). You can learn more about the [PayPal Privacy Policy here](https://cms.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US).
> 
> **Contests**  
>  Digital Family may offer from time to time offer voluntary, optional contests in which we request certain personal information, including the user’s name, e-mail address, company name, job title/function, and the other information specific to the contest. The information gathered in the entry form is used to verify the entrant’s identity, to send the entrant an e-mail notification that his or her entry has been received, and to contact winners and/or prize recipients. Under no circumstances will Artesian Media, Inc. divulge this information to a third party.
> 
> Because the rules and terms of each contest can vary, all information about each contest is clearly posted during the event. All contests are conducted in full accordance with United States federal and state laws.
> 
> **_We never divulge contact or other personal information to third parties._**

**How DigitalFamily uses the information it gathers/tracks**

DigitalFamily uses any information voluntarily provided by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like, based on traffic to those areas. DigitalFamily does not track what each user reads, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us to continue to build a better service for you.

DigitalFamily creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Because DigitalFamily doesn’t track the usage patterns of individual users, an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked on a specific ad.

**With whom does DigitalFamily share the information it gathers/tracks?**

Artesian Media uses the information described above to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience’s demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We do not share information about individual users with any third party.

The Artesian Media sites contain links to third party sites. Artesian Media is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers or any other site we link to, uses information about you when you click through to its site, please contact that site directly.

Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name and e-mail addresses) on any comments, bulletin boards, or in chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties.

**What is DigitalFamily’s opt-out policy?**

DigitalFamily gives users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * Opting not to receive any informational mailings when accessing any special sections of our sites, including the Readers Corner.
  * Opting not to provide certain personal information when completing an online form, subscribing to a publication, or participating in a contest.
  * Opting not to email us, order any of our products, or subscribe our newsletter, which eliminates the need for any personally identifying information from our users.

**_If you would like us to remove your name from our mailing list, please email  [Janine@DigitalFamily.com.](mailto:Janine@DigitalFamily.com.)_**

**What is  the DigitalFamily policy for updating, deleting or deactivating names from its database?**

****Users may unsubscribe to any of our publications or ask to be deleted from all Artesian Media mailing lists by sending an e-mail to ** _[Janine@DigitalFamily.com](mailto:Janine@DigitalFamily.com.)_** , by calling us at  323-935-0115 or by sending mail to:

Artesian Media, Inc.  
P.O. Box 36419  
Los Angeles, California 90036

**For additional information:**

Users who are experiencing problems or who have any questions about how our sites work can email [Janine@DigitalFamily.com](mailto:Janine@DigitalFamily.com).

Users who have questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site can email [Janine@DigitalFamily.com](mailto:Janine@DigitalFamily.com) or by phone at  323-935-0115 or by ground mail to:

Janine C. Warner  
CEO & President  
Artesian Media, Inc.  
P.O. Box 36419  
Los Angeles, California 90036
